A Guide to the Henry Luce Foundation records, Record Group 3, Accession 2017:059 FA1410
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Luce Fund for Asian Studies, 1975-2013; 2
  - Early Grants, 1975-1987; 5
    - University of Washington - Japan Literacy Censorship during Allied Occupation, 1980-1985 (Box 85, Folder 541)
    - University of Washington - Democratic People's Republic of Korea and the United States, 1981-1985 (Box 85, Folder 542)
    - University of Washington - Rejected Proposals, 1975-1979 (Box 85, Folder 543-544)
    - University of Washington - Financial Statements, 1978 (Box 85, Folder 545)
    - University of Washington - Resume File, undated (Box 85, Folder 546)
    - Yale University - Southeast Asia Refugee Project, 1981-1984 (Box 85, Folder 547)
    - Yale University - Chinese Agricultural Development and United States-China Trade (Box 85, Folder 548)
    - Yale University - Rejected Proposals, 1976-1977 (Box 86, Folder 549)
    - Yale University - Financial Statements, 1975-1979 (Box 86, Folder 550)
    - Yale University - Resume File, undated (Box 86, Folder 551)
    - Yale University - General Correspondence, 1975-1984 (Box 86, Folder 552)
    - Yale University - Bilateral Trade Issues, 1977-1985 (Box 86, Folder 553)